Sohal Patel

www.linkedin.com/in/sohal-patel

502.608.6102 / spatel11uk@gmail.com

EDUCATION

University of Louisville, College of Business

Expected December 2020

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration in Computer Information Systems Concentration in Web Development

Jefferson Community and Technical College Associate in Science

May 2018 GPA of 3.8

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Managed businesses of different sizes and performed with the least waste of time and effort. Experienced in managing projects, increasing efficiency, providing excellent customer satisfaction, and coding inventory systems for POS systems. Effectively communicates with employees at all levels to meet operational goals.

SPECIALIZED SKILLS

C# programming Multilingual

Html programming Managing store inventory and performance Python programming Microsoft Office Specialists Certifications

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

Brick Bridge Consulting, Software Developer

January 2020 - Present

- Building applications for Podio and automate the Podio process using Globiflow.
- Writing C# function to make application for Citrix Workspace that uses Al.
- Managing Amazon DynamoDB for Podio application.

Jr Mini Mart, Manager

June 2015 - Present

- Managing Inventory and Order items weekly for the whole store.
- · Managing employees' payrolls.
- Managing weekly scan of data for the store and making sure all data are correct and are processed correctly in the system.
- Made a C# program to be able to calculate Marlboro Scan Data submission and validate data for each week.

Academy Sports + Outdoors, Customer Service

October 2015 - December 2019

- Managed PDQ and provided excellent customer service.
- Covered the Cashier Team Lead position and counted down register till to make sure they correctly showed the correct value in the system.

Subway, Manager

August 2013 - May 2015

- Hired and trained employees.
- Facilitated planning & executed weekly order.
- Reviewed employee's performance and helped them improve certain areas.
- Trained new employees to make sandwiches and how to interact with customers.
- Assisted with philanthropy and events rooted in giving back to the local community.